https://www.womenofthehall.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from our visitors.
To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails. The e-mail address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. Note: If at any time, you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from the National Women’s Hall of Fame, you may follow the detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of one of our emails.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order, or when you enter, submit or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive / credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems. These parties are required to keep this information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For example, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our rights or the rights, property, or safety of others. Note: Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, changes will be posted on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:
Copyright © 2020All Rights Reserved.National Women’s Hall of Fame.
1 Canal StreetPost Office Box 335Seneca Falls, NY 13148Phone (315) 568-8060
Shop at AmazonSmile and Amazon will make a donation to the National Women’s Hall of Fame
Get started
